User.create(email: 'guest@gmail.com', password: 'password')
User.create(email: 'KenJennings@gmail.com', password: 'password')
User.create(email: 'timyates@gmail.com', password: 'timyates')
User.create(email: 'markthompson@gmail.com', password: 'markthompson')
User.create(email: 'johnhamlin@gmail.com', password: 'johnhamlin')
User.create(email: 'brookejones@gmail.com', password: 'brookejones')
User.create(email: 'alisonchristine@gmail.com', password: 'alisonchristine')

Card.create!(question: 'What is the center of the atom called?', answer: 'The nucleus', deck_id: 1)
Card.create!(question: 'At room temperature, what is the only metal in liquid form?', answer: 'mercury', deck_id: 1)
Card.create!(question: 'Is sodium hydroxide (NaOH) an acid or base?', answer: 'base', deck_id: 1)
Card.create!(question: 'The great Victoria Desert is located in...?', answer: 'Australia', deck_id: 2)
Card.create!(question: 'Name the 5 Great Lakes in the U.S.', answer: 'Lakes Superior, Michigan, Huron, Erie, and Ontario', deck_id: 2)
Card.create!(question: 'What is the capital of Albania', answer: 'Tirana', deck_id: 2)
Card.create!(question: 'What was the name of the company Steve Jobs founded after getting fired from Apple?', answer: 'NeXT', deck_id: 3)
Card.create!(question: 'What was the original inspiration for the Mac\'s GUI?', answer: 'Steve Jobs visit to Xerox PARC in 1979', deck_id: 3)
Card.create!(question: 'What American electrical engineer is known as the \'father of information theory\'', answer: 'Claude Shannon. Many say he founded and formalized information theory with a landmark paper titled \'A Mathematical Theory of Communcation\' published in 1948', deck_id: 3)
Card.create!(question: 'This person created a machine called The Analytical Engine. His ideas were some of the first that led to the creation of computers', answer: 'Charles Babbage', deck_id: 3)
Card.create!(question: 'Who led the Manhatten Project?', answer: 'Robert Oppenheimer', deck_id: 4)
Card.create!(question: 'What element was used at the core of the \'Fat Man\' atomic bomb created by the United States?', answer: 'Plutonium', deck_id: 4)
Card.create!(question: 'Who led Germany\'s effort to create the atomic bomb?', answer: 'Werner Heisenberg', deck_id: 4)
Card.create!(question: 'What is a tendon?', answer: 'Fibrous collagen that links muscle to bone', deck_id: 5)
Card.create!(question: 'What 6 elements make up almost 99% of the human body?', answer: 'oxygen, carbon, hydrogen, nitrogen, calcium, phosphorus', deck_id: 5)
Card.create!(question: 'What is the purpose of the endocrine system?', answer: 'Secrete hormones into the blood. These hormones travel to different tissues and regulate various bodily functions', deck_id: 5)
Card.create!(question: 'Name the major industries dominated by the following industrialists: Rockefeller, Morgan, Carnegie, Vanderbilt, Ford', answer: 'Oil, Finance, Steel, Railroads (Steamships earlier in life), Automobiles', deck_id: 6)
Card.create!(question: 'What was the name of John D. Rockefeller\'s company?', answer: 'Standard Oil', deck_id: 6)
Card.create!(question: 'This man bought Carnegie Steel in 1901 for $400 million and set up U.S. Steel. Who was this man?', answer: 'J.P. Morgan. Following the sale, $226 million went to Andrew Carnegie himself', deck_id: 6)

Deck.create!(title: 'General Chemistry', description: 'Gen Chem 101 Flashcards', author_id: 1)
Deck.create!(title: 'Geography', description: 'Geography of the world', author_id: 1)
Deck.create!(title: 'Computer History', author_id: 1)
Deck.create!(title: 'Atomic Age', description: 'AP History - The events and innovations that led to the creation of the most lethal weapon of all time', author_id: 1)
Deck.create!(title: 'Anatomy', author_id: 1)
Deck.create!(title: 'Gilded Age', description: 'Captains of Industry or Robber Barons?', author_id: 1)
